<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Volunteer Projects Ceylon Japan]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Volunteer Projects Ceylon Japan]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/volunteer-projects-ceylon-japan/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 04:04:37 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/volunteer-projects-ceylon-japan/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 04:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why Volunteer Projects Ceylon?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Why Volunteer Projects Ceylon?</h1><p>VPC is an innovative and leading charity organisation devoted to providing life-changing placements in Sri Lanka for overseas volunteers.

Bringing together the different talents of highly experienced and award-winning charity professionals who have worked in the field for over 20 years, we have created a charity team who are truly passionate about social and community development. Since its very first day, VPC has striven to place people at the heart of all we do: from our multi-national and multi-talented volunteers who change people's lives on a daily basis, to the many communities whose lives are changed.

We believe that by working together, regardless of age, gender, nationality or social background, we can create the richest of experiences, develop valuable knowledge and skills through complete cultural immersion. Above all else, though, each of us is relentless in our mission to offer hope and opportunity for those people in communities who need it most – and each and every day we feel immensely proud of our volunteers' tireless work towards achieving our mission.</p><img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/453cfca063dfbdf07225c016b2d0b770/croprotate.jpg?cropheight=192&cropwidth=225&degrees=0&input=https%3A%2F%2Fthe-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com%2F224ee750-2bb0-40e4-909e-5fe2d4ac65b8.jpg&x=0&y=16"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/volunteer-projects-ceylon-japan/why-volunteer-projects-ceylon/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">12fe018a-e596-4480-b5ba-eff5fc6109fa</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 04:04:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Two Weeks Program]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Two Weeks Program</h1><p>Whether you are taking time off from school,work or just need a small career-break, there is always a way for you to squeeze a week or two adventure into your schedule.</p><img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/053ce097-03e2-4b4f-8e88-003d273bf417.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/volunteer-projects-ceylon-japan/two-weeks-program/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">01f44733-d4dd-4d9a-8a2f-00f89f1a5fc9</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 04:02:34 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>